TUSHAR HUDKAR

User Experience Designer

Hello, I'm User Experience Designer with experience in comprehensive understanding of design process in all the design stages of product including Research & Front-end Development. I seek to join a team that values product research, design, collaboration and provides plenty of opportunity to tackle challenging problems and to innovate.

- hudkar.design
- tusharhudkar3@gmail.com
- +91 9560855095
 - Gurugram

EXPERIENCE

UX Designer & Front-End Developer

Foodraveller, Gurugram July 2016 - Present

- Work closely with cross functional team of designers, developers, stakeholders and product managers.
- Created the entire user interface of the responsive web application of foodraveller including conceptualization, wireframing and front-end development.
- Provide design support at all stages of the design process.
- Developed and improved the interaction design, micro-interaction and process across web and mobile.
- Analyzed user feedback, analytics and data to identify opportunity for improvement of the user experience.
- Implement design with cross-browser support for various plateform.
- O Control and maintain the design standard of the product.
- Capable of identifying and improving usability issue.
- Experience with A/B testing and determine the effectiveness of proposed site change.

UX Researcher & Front-End Developer

1Thing Design & Innovation Private Limited, Gurugram November 2013 - March 2016

- Responsible for competitive analysis, contextual inquiry and design research.
- Researching and developing ideas for new products and consistently deliver inspiring concept-driven design through all phases and projects.
- Observed and interviewed user to better understand, document their need and acted as a customer advocate in product and design decision.
- Create UX workflow, wireframes, interactive prototype for web and mobile and iterated to provide the best user experience solution and suggestion.
- Conduct design review with internal, external design and development team to ensure proposal solution elegantly & intuitively met product objective and user need.
- Test prototype and monitor customer feedback.
- Able to quickly transition from product spec & wireframes to design and front-end development.

SKILLS

User Experience Design
Interaction Design
User Research
Usability Testing
Prototyping
Front-End Development

UX METHOD

Ethnography
Contextual Inquiry
Competitive Evaluations
Persona, Scenarios
Strategy Development
Sketching, Site Mapping
Information Architecture
Brainstorming
Usability Testing
Heuristic Evaluation
Prototyping

TOOLS

Sketch, Photoshop InVision, Marvel Figma

WEB DEVELOPMENT

HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Foundation, SASS, JQuery Task Runner: - Grunt & Gulp

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering in Electronics & Communication IES College Of Technology Bhopal 2008 - 2012